messageboard.com 2000-12-04

# TeacherReviews.com: Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

* * *

TeacherReviews.com is run by students, not some big corporation doing everything possible to make a buck.   We have no intention of selling or abusing your personal information, especially for monetary gain.  Everybody on the TeacherReviews.com team has an email address, and we all receive spam.   We will not add to this problem by sending spam to your email address, nor let other companies have access to your email address so they could do just that.  

TeacherReviews is a community by students and for students, and it's a Web site that you should feel comfortable at.  We have listed bellow everything that we can think of relating to your personal information.  If you have any questions, please [contact us](mailto:webmaster@teacherreviews.com).

****

**  
personal information**

At TeacherReviews.com, we intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. In general, you can visit the  sites without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may need information from you, such as your email address. It is our intent to let you know before we collect personal information from you on the Internet.

If you choose to give us personal information -- for example to add a review or enter a contest -- it is our intent to let you know how we will use such information. If you tell us that you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes. We do keep track of the domains from which people visit us. We analyze this data for trends and statistics, and then we discard it.

TeacherReviews is the sole owner of the information gathered on our Web site.  Described below are the methods which TeacherReviews uses the information collected.  It is our policy NOT to sell or distribute any personally identifiable information.

**

email and spam

**

When creating a user account, TeacherReviews will ask you for your email address.  We use this to verify who you are.  This is done by sending you a unique email verification key.  If you do not put in your valid email address, you will not get this email and your reviews will not be made public.  Without this feature, the credibility of the reviews would be too questionable to be reliable. 

This is the primary reason why we request your email address.  We may also use it to give you warnings, important news, or, of course, if you are one of the contest winners.

We will never send unsolicited email to you, nor will we sell your email address to anybody.  

**  
cookies**

There is a technology called "cookies" which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. TeacherReviews use cookies so that we can better serve you when you return to our site. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it.

How TeacherReviews uses cookies:

  * To optionally remember your logon, so that you can automatically be logged on next time you visit the site.

  * To optionally remember your school, so next time you visit the site we can bring you directly to your school's page.

  * For when you log in, so that we the system knows who you are from page to page. 

Data stored in TeacherReviews cookies cannot be seen by other Web sites.  

**  
links to other sites**

Our site may contain links to other sites. These other sites may send cookies to users, collect data, or solicit individual information. These sites or services also have separate data and privacy practices independent of TeacherReviews and TeacherReviews disclaims any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

When we link to other sites, we do not pass your personal information to those sites. 

**

security precautions

**

Your individual user information is password protected. We recommend that you do not share your password with anyone. While TeacherReviews strives to protect your individual information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to TeacherReviews and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information.

**

contacting us

**

If at any time you believe that TeacherReviews has not adhered to these principles, please notify at [webmaster@TeacherReviews.com](mailto:webmaster@teacherreviews.com).

We will use all reasonable efforts to determine and correct the problem.
